<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Heron</string>
    <!--  BluetoothChat -->
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="not_connected">You are not connected to a device</string>
    <string name="bt_not_enabled_leaving">Bluetooth was not enabled. Leaving Bluetooth Chat.</string>
    <string name="title_connecting">connecting...</string>
    <string name="title_connected_to">connected: </string>
    <string name="title_not_connected">not connected</string>

    <!--  DeviceListActivity -->
    <string name="scanning">scanning for devices...</string>
    <string name="select_device">select a device to connect</string>
    <string name="none_paired">No devices have been paired</string>
    <string name="none_found">No devices found</string>
    <string name="title_paired_devices">Paired Devices</string>
    <string name="title_other_devices">Other Available Devices</string>
    <string name="button_scan">Scan for devices</string>

    <!-- Options Menu -->
    <string name="connect">Connect a device</string>
    <string name="discoverable">Make discoverable</string>

    <!-- Options Menu -->
    <string name="Instructions1"> On First installation, press the "start service" button below to begin monitoring
        (this will start automatically on-boot in the future). \n\nA pop-up message will request permission to screen capture - grant permission and check "do not show again."
        The "start service" button can be used at any time if it has stopped due to errors or other reasons. \n\nBe sure to enable the permissions for "Record Audio" and "Usage Access" requested during install. Make sure this device is paired
        with the administrator phone to allow for future data transfer. </string>

    <string name="Instructions2"> It is best to obtain concurrence from the monitored user. Alternatively, you will need to enforce bluetooth pairing through disbling access to settings </string>
    <string name="Instructions3"> Currently, Android does not allow any app to prevent the user from uninstalling it through safe mode. Scoped will alert you if it appears the companion app has not run in the last 24 hours. </string>
    <string name="Instructions4"> Third party apps with root access may provide stricter installation control on the monitored phone. Alternatively, we recommend revoking device access unless the monitored user agrees to installation</string>


    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior" translatable="false">android.support.design.widget.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>

    <string name="adminhelp"> Select the monitored device under \"target devices\" to view and retrieve monitored screenshots/videos. Press \"retrieve data\" to download files. Press the Calendar icon to adjust download settings</string>
    <string name="calendar"> Maximum Files to Receive</string>


    <string-array name="options">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
        <item>Help &amp; Feedback</item>
        <item>Subscription</item>
    </string-array>



</resources>
